Good morning.
I'm going now.
Okay, travel safely.
Hey! Morning, Tani!
Yamada-kun.
Yes, I'm Yamada!
YES,
I'M
YAMADA
Did Suzuki-san tell you anything?
Hey, you have good instincts.
Well, when you suddenly pop up
with that kind of energy...
BEING MY
PAL'S PAL MEANS
WE'RE ALL BUDS
It's the "If you like Suzuki, then you're
probably fine with me, too" theory.
I hadn't planned on telling anyone.
Huh? Why not?
Because I don't want to tarnish
Suzuki-san's reputation.
Huh?
What?
You mean you think Suzuki's reputation
is so elevated that it could tank?
That's hilarious.
But I guess you would, Tani!
Man, that's love.
If Suzuki says it's fine,
then it's fine, right?
Besides, she said, "I'm in love with Tani-kun!"
and ran out of the classroom yesterday.
What?
I mean, how can anyone do anything
but support that, right?
Satou and Watanabe and Kabacho, too!
Who's that last one?
Oh! And Suzuki's reputation
or whatever isn't gonna change,
but my opinion of your entertainment
value has increased, Tani!
Entertainment value?
Yamada-kun, you're easy to talk to.
What's this? Flattery will get you nowhere.
I'll give you some candy. Here.
I did get something.
That much?
And then...
that's when SudaKen hugged the heroine,
whispering "I love you" in her ear.
The scene was so awesome!
DON'T CARE...
What's with those expressions?
I really couldn't care less
about fiction right now.
You have some more important
updates for us, don't you?
With my shojo-manga-turned-live-action mania,
I do want to talk about it.
It's
precious
to me...
That's an interesting form of mania.
Suzuki, you were always all SudaKen this and
SudaKen that, giving off troublemaker vibes,
but the truth is...
GRIN
Right?
Exactly.
Still...
That was no way to interact
with the guy you like.
I am all too aware of that.
You weren't playing catch in your
conversation. You were striking him out.
ALL ONE-SIDED!
EEK
How about this article as a reference?
Conversational
Techniques for
Those Who
Want to Be Loved
Be a good listener. Talking nonstop
only about yourself is no good!
TENSE...
SMILE...
BE A GOOD LISTENER !
( Trying to make small talk
with relatable anecdotes )
Ask good questions.
ASK GOOD QUESTIONS ! !
Ask about things the other
person might want to talk about.
Show that you're paying attention.
SHOW YOU'RE PAYING ATTENTION ! ! !
Leaving them hanging in silence
might make them uneasy.
Reply when the timing is appropriate.
I'm totally awful.
Girlfriend.
Boyfriend.
Couple.
ACK
Stop suddenly re-realizing and freaking out.
This is crazy. I'm so happy!
For some reason, I'm annoyed.
But, since it's started,
that means there's an end, too.
All the emotions.
Fine!
I'll do it, then!
I'll become the ultimate girlfriend!
You don't have to pretend
to be a Jump character.
So, what's this ultimate girlfriend gonna do?
Today... I'll say, "Let's walk home together."
You're adorable.
Tani-kun!
Is it okay for us to hang out here like normal?
Wha?!
It's fine. Please don't let it bother you.
Hear that, Suzuki?
What? That makes me feel so alone!
Don't mind him!
Should I have said it wasn't all right?
I was lying! I'm sorry!
Tani-kun, that was quite the fastball.
Come on, Suzuki. Say it!
What? Now?
U-Um, well...
STARE
It's no good! I can feel myself
losing consciousness!
I can't
look him
in the eye...
Huh? Did you commence some kind of battle?
Um, Tani-kun...
Today... should we walk home together?
AFTER SCHOOL
WHOMP
Walking home together from the
classroom is really nerve-racking!
WHOMP
We're here, too, though.
Up to
the
school
gate.
Suzuki! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Cheers!
Oh, Reina! Practice hard!
Suzuki, I see you can do the
box step now! It's weird though.
That's unreal. No one sees Tani.
SILENCE
"Talking nonstop
only about yourself
is no good!!"
"Ask about things
the other person
might want to talk about!!!"
ASK GOOD QUESTIONS
BE A GOOD LISTENER
Now that I'm really paying attention,
I really did just make him listen
to whatever I wanted to say.
And what is Tani-kun interested in?
I have no idea!
FWIP
Huh? It looks like Tani-kun
might want to say something.
Verily, this is...
ASK GOOD
QUESTIONS
What? What is it?
BARGES IN!
Oh, it's just, um...
It's nothing.
Huh?
I feel like I got something wrong.
HMMM...
The more I think about it,
the less I know what to do.
Is being with me right now fun for Tani-kun?
And this is where we part ways.
It feels like I wasted some potential.
Well...
Suzuki-san, do you have a little more time?
Yeah!
Leaving them hanging in
silence might make them uneasy?
SHOW YOU'RE
PAYING ATTENTION!!!
This morning, Yamada-kun talked to me.
What? Did he say something he shouldn't have?
No. Actually, he was really friendly.
HUH?
He can be overly friendly.
*BOOMERANG
And, because I thought that hiding this was
the best option... I was a little surprised.
I'm sorry! Should I have hidden everything?
It's just, yesterday, my emotions boiled up
and over and I blurted everything out!
Boiled up and over?
Oh, he's laughing.
WHEW
No, I don't mind either way.
It doesn't bother me.
But, Suzuki-san, you said you did mind,
so I wasn't sure if it was okay.
Ugh, seriously...
Tani-kun, this side of you is so...
I'm an idiot.
My head is so full of rules and
conventions meant for other people
TRAITS OF LONG-
LASTING COUPLES
10 RULES
5 TRAITS OF WOMEN WHO
ARE LOVED BY OTHERS
that I can't even hold a conversation.
I haven't even really looked at the person
right in front of me, have I?
That stuff doesn't bother me!
I mean, not long ago, I might've minded, but...
I want to live proudly,
saying that I like what I like!
That's the kind of policy
I'm living my life by right now!
STUNNED
Sorry. Did I fail full force just now?
Oh. No.
Suzuki-san, do you have time this weekend?
Huh?
BA-DUMP
If you'd like, then maybe...
You mentioned it before...
Grabbing hamburgers...
The hamburgers...
That's crazy! We harmonized!
It's like telepathy!
I thought it'd be nice if we could go.
Yeah, yeah! Let's go! For sure!
And if we're going, let's go
somewhere it's easy to hang out!
I'll look it up, then.
girlfriend conversation
conversation how to keep up
Wait, wait, wait right there!
GNNNNN
Hold up!
Crumple
Hey, I need a minute.
I can't.
It's not true, is it, Tani-kun?
This couldn't get any worse.
How pathetic can I be?
That's devastatingly adorable, though!
Please just forget it.
Nope! Can't do that! I'm never gonna forget!
The fact that you think about me when
I'm not around makes me way too happy!
I thought that I might be the only one who's
all excited and spinning in circles, so...
Suzuki-san.
I love you.
I hadn't properly told you yet,
so I wanted to put it into words.
Huh? What?
The thing that he wanted to
tell me earlier... Could this be it?
POOF
Steam?
Suzuki is made of 60 percent water!
HEART-FLUTTERING
DISGORGEMENT
Everyone is.
Let's go watch a movie, too!
You've already looked them up, right?
(Really, truly embarrassed)
Kill me.
Why?
I hit that anguish too hard,
so my throat's all dry.
Hit the anguish too hard?
If I sang right now, I bet I'd sound cool!
Suzuki-san, would you like a candy?
What? I want it!
Tani-kun, all kinds of things come out of
your pockets, huh? Thanks!
A festival of
handkerchiefs
This is yummy!
Oh, no. That was...
GASP
I feel like someone's talking about me!
No one would do that.
I'm so happy for you.
Oh, I can't wait for our first date!
I can't imagine you and Tani-kun
walking around out there together.
That's true.
Take pictures for us.
What?!
Candid shots of Tani-kun?
Hardly. Shots of the two of you!
What? No! I couldn't!
I'd be too embarrassed!
Suzuki, I never know when
your embarrassment will kick in.
But it's true that Suzuki's bad
at smiling for photos, right?
FORCED
They often say that dimples
are pit traps for love.
Can you even interpret those as dimples?
So that's why you're always
making those silly faces.
It's a big step, so you need
to make some good memories.
Yeah, true.
That said...
What on earth should I wear?
This probably
isn't right...
I don't know what kind of
clothes Tani-kun likes,
so I just need something generally cute
that most people would like.
(MEETING AT 12)
I was so anxious, I ended up
arriving thirty minutes early.
EVERYONE LOVES
BABY PANDAS
*THE RESULT OF OVERTHINKING
I'm starting to get nervous! I'm gonna be
covered in sweat before we meet up!
Should I duck into a shop?
No, I'd hate it if I relaxed too much
and kept Tani-kun waiting.
I wonder what Tani-kun will be wearing.
FLUFFY
Train of
thought
derailed
Suzuki-san.
T-Tani-kun!
Sorry. Did I keep you waiting?
He looks pretty much the same as always!
(Pretty much anything'll work)
SQUEEEEE!
Regular
Clothes
School
Uniform
If you'd contacted me, I'd have hurried.
No, I didn't want to rush you!
Actually, you're really early, Tani-kun!
It's because I wanted to get here
about ten minutes early.
You're twenty minutes early.
Oh, here it is! Here it is!
The volume of it is amazing, right?
It is amazing.
Thank you for this meal!
Huh? Hang on.
FREEZE
When I came here before...
Wow, look at you digging in!
Yum!
Stare...
STARE
What is it?
It's just, I was watching you and thinking,
"Tani-kun is eating that really well."
I'm not a little kid.
Suzuki-san, aren't you going to eat?
I'm eating! I'm eating!
NIBBLE
Just
the
bun
CHOMP
DRAG
The
whole
thing
came
out
MUNCH
You eat one filling at a time?
It's too embarrassing to open
my mouth wide to take a bite!
Maybe it's one of those
unfeminine things.
I'm sorry. But...
whatever's most delicious is best, isn't it?
You're not wrong.
I'll just go ahead and dig in, then!
Mmm, yum!
We've got time before the movie,
so should we wander around?
Tani-kun, is there anything you want to buy,
or any shops you want to go to?
No.
Then can we just look around wherever?
Yeah.
Oh, it's already time!
Recording video and audio
inside the theater is a crime.
EXCITED
By law, a minimum of ten years...
STARE...
Sorry. What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
THE END
See you later!
It was the kind of movie with
a bonus after the credit roll!
I cried a little in there.
A little?
Sorry! I've gotta go cut some hedges.
*She's
"picking
flowers"
Weepy Eyes
Whoa, that's ugly.
Hurry, hurry! If I'm in here too long,
it could invite another misunderstanding!
Sorry, Tani-kun! Thanks for waiting.
THE NORTH WITCH
AND THE YETI
BOOM
Take pictures for us.
Excuse me. Could you take a picture for us?
Okay, taking it now!
I can't do it!
I could never endure the time between
asking someone and the shutter click!
Suzuki-san.
GASP
Want to check that shop?
Yeah!
Oh! It's the fluffball that was in the movie!
The yeti.
They have the witch and the bears, too!
Wow!
So, tell me...
How would does buying
something to remember today
rate in terms of femininty?
Seven hundred million points!
700,000,000 POINTS
How do those points work?
The North Witch
and the Yeti
It's totally possible to make memories
even without a photo, right?
That... town? The place where the main
character grew up was so pretty, wasn't it?
Halcyon Town?
Yeah, that's it!
And the images of North
whatever were pretty, too!
North Island.
The cutest one was the little fluffball.
The yeti.
But that scene where the whole
family gathered was so cute!
I forgot their names, though.
Gotek, Nitt, Boa, Goden, Heetek.
What? Tani-kun, you remember a ton!
That's crazy!
Suzuki-san, did you really watch the movie?
What?
That's so mean! I totally watched it!
I'm just not good at remembering
names and details!
It really moved me! I felt it in my heart!
And I cried during every scene with a song.
You did cry.
And also...
That part where the witch left the house and
cast magic on the... yeti without looking...
Just "whoosh," I loved that!
And even though she only drinks black
coffee, she put milk and sugar in it...
and she made that beautiful omurice.
She's just a major tsundere, right?
It was so cute!
Really?
Yes, really. It was onscreen off to
the side, but just for a split second.
And they only showed it
for a second at the end,
but the number of dishes on that table!
There were enough for all of them,
so I thought, "Oh, they'll all
be together forever."
It made me so happy.
SORTING
MEMORIES
I see. So that's what all that meant.
I see. That's what...
It was a good movie, wasn't it?
You realize that now?!
Hey, Tani-kun...
Did you really watch the movie?
HEH
I'm sorry.
I guess the movie didn't really
strike a chord for Tani-kun.
Somehow, it feels like it went by in a flash.
I was nervous, but it was so much fun!
I ate what I wanted to eat,
went to the shops I wanted to,
saw a movie I wanted to see...
HUH...?
Huh?
Was it all geared toward me?
And we've arrived.
Today is ending.
It'd be nice if the way home
stretched out longer.
Um, today...
was a lot of fun!
Although...
PSHHHHH...
I might have dragged you around a bit.
Suzuki-san.
Today, the shops we went to,
the movie we watched...
They were all things I wouldn't
have picked for myself,
but I really had a lot of fun.
Even if I went to the same places
we did today and did the same things...
I'm certain I wouldn't have enjoyed
it like I did today without you.
So, um, basically...
It was fun because I was with you,
Suzuki-san. Thank you.
Tani-kun.
I want to take a picture together!
Huh? Here?
Anywhere is fine!
When I look back at it, I want to
remember that this day was our first date,
that we had a lot of fun,
that my heart was racing... stuff like that.
Like a keepsake. You know?
Then, um...
What do I do?
T-Tani-kun, you stand here!
Oh, move your face a little more this way.
Okay. I'm taking it.
Bye, Tani-kun!
See you at school!
STARE...
Pandas are cute, aren't they?
Huh? You like them?
Yeah. I like them.
LIKE
*Pandas
That makes me so happy!
What is this? I mean, of course
I feel this way about Tani-kun,
but I feel like I might start liking
myself more with this sparkly feeling!
Right now... I feel like
I might be the ultimate!
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Dinner isn't ready yet!
That's totally fine!
I'm gonna look back at that photo!
You're kidding me.
GLOOM...